Guide to the Henry Herbert Knibbs Papers, 1874-1945
Department of Special Collections
- Section VI: Oversize
  - Carton of tearsheets and whole number periodicals, including the following:
    - Tearsheets. Poems, unless otherwise indicated:
      - Fugitive
      - Gambler's Choice
      - The Game Popular Magazine, 6/7/16.
      - The Gold Diggers
      - The Gringo Renegade Popular Magazine, 7/1/29.
      - The Hunted Man
      - Indigo Pete's J.B.
      - Jan of Sutra Blue Book, 6/29.
      - Keeper of the Gate
      - The Last of the Cavaliers 5/16.
      - The Last Relay
      - The Last Ride of Little Smoke Popular Magazine, 3/20/17
      - Man-O-War
      - Mesa Magic Popular Magazine, 8/20/15.
      - The Mule Drivers Smart Set, 5/14.
      - My Heart's Desire Smart Set, 6/14.
      - Nothing to Do But Go
      - The Optimist
      - Out There Somewhere
      - Outlaw and Outlaw Brother
      - Pearl of the Atolls Popular Magazine, 8/20/16.
      - Pericles' Honeymoon ss Sat. Eve. Post, 8/19/33,p. 5.
      - Pony Express Popular Magazine, 2/20/17.
      - The Rain Makers 10/10/22.
      - The Real Romance
      - The Reata
      - Reciprocity Popular Magazine, 11/20/15.
      - Riders of the Stars American Magazine, 8/16.
      - Robert's House Short Stories, 8/10/21.
      - The Round Corral
      - Saddle Songs
      - Smoky
      - The Snow Angel ss Popular Magazine, 12/20/29 & 1/2/30.
      - Stallion Gray
      - Stallions of the Storm Adventure, 8/1/30.
      - Tang of Life Popular Magazine, 2/20/17.
      - The Tenderfoot
      - That Colt Pericles Sat. Eve. Post, 5/21/32pg. 12.
      - That Roan Cayuse
      - They Tried to Frame Yardlow ss Short Stories, 7/29.pg. 47.
      - Three Swinging Shadow West
      - Tonto Charley Adventure, 8/15/29.
      - Trail to Glory 10/29/30,pg. 96.
      - The Trail Makers
      - The Two Saddles
      - Walkin John Short Stories, 2/25/34.
      - We Aim to Please 11/11/31.
      - The West Popular Magazine, 10/7/16.
      - Where the Ponies Come to Drink
      - Why Pericles Sat. Eve. Post, 4/1/33,pg. 24.
      - Yeabo's Adventure
      - Young Hardesty Circulates Adventure, July,pg. 53.
    - Misc. Periodicals:
      - Argosy 2/26/38.
      - Blue Book 9/38.
      - Frontier Stories Spring, 1937.
      - Sat. Eve. Post 8/16/30.
      - 8/20/38.
      - 9/3/38
    - Tearsheets: Other Authors
      - Memorial to Gene Rhodes Sat. Eve. Post, 8/20/38,pg 21.
      - The Proud Sheriff by Rhodes Sat. Eve. Post, 10/1/32.pg 3.
      - Interesting Westerners
      - In the Forefront 10/18.
      - Advertisement of H. H. K.'s Songs of the Lost Frontier.
      - Mitre Press book advertisements
      - Red Breath by Foster-Harris
      - Section from Popular Magazine
- Shelved elsewhere: Knibbs, Henry Herbert, Síla Zivota, Polish edition of work, 1932.